syndaver.com 2017-12-15

# Privacy Policy | SynDaver Labs

## General

This Privacy Policy (Policy) sets forth the SynDaver™ Labs (SYNDAVER, we, or us) policies regarding the collection and use of information relating to the SYNDAVER web site located at www.syndaver.com (Site). When we refer to SYNDAVER, we or us, we mean our entire company, including our affiliates and subsidiaries.

Certain areas of the Site may contain information intended only for licensed medical professionals or members of the medical device and pharmaceutical industry. Accordingly, SYNDAVER reserves the right to limit certain areas of the Site to those persons who register and meet the qualifications imposed by us. This Policy addresses our privacy practices relating to the use of our Site.

## Personal Information

Personally Identifiable Information (Personal Information) is information that can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name, email address, telephone number or similar information. SYNDAVER only collects Personal Information that you choose to share with us, such as when (1) contacting us via the Site (by clicking on the “Contact Us” link at the top of each web page), (2) submitting your resume online in response to a job posting, (3) registering online for an event, course, or promotion, or, (4) upon registration for access to those areas of our Site intended only for medical industry professionals.

## Registered Users

If you are an industry professional, to register, you must provide us with certain Personal Information, including your name, email address, postal mail address, title and industry affiliation. We will use this Personal Information to review and verify your registration information. We may use your Personal Information to send periodic marketing or promotional notices to you or notify you of any changes to this Policy. You can always opt-out of receiving these communications from us by following the “opt-out” procedures described below.

## Uses

Any information you provide to SYNDAVER must be true, accurate, current, and non-misleading for the purpose for which you are providing it. And, if you are a registered user you must have the authority to provide the information submitted to and through the Site, and understand and agree that we may from time to time verify such authority.In particular we may need to contact you directly to verify the authenticity of business transactions.

If your Personal Information is submitted through the Site when applying for a position with SYNDAVER, your Personal Information will be used solely for the purpose of accepting and evaluating you for the position. We may retain your Personal Information for a period of time, but only for the purpose of considering your application for current or future positions at SYNDAVER. This information may be shared within SYNDAVER as well as with third party service providers contracted by us to collect and maintain candidate submissions for job postings.

If you contact SYNDAVER via the Site, we will use the Personal Information contained in your email to respond to your specific inquiry or comments in the email. In some cases we may also add you to our general email list, but will never transfer this Personal Information, including your email address to a third party. You can always opt-out of receiving any communications from us by following the “opt-out” procedures described below.

## Tracking

The Site automatically tracks certain information about your behavior while visiting the Site. The information gathered includes only the URL from which you accessed this Site, and which URL you visit next. We collect and store this aggregate information in order to measure the Site’s performance and improve the Site’s design and functionality. If you are a registered user, we may use your Usage Data without your Personal Information, in order to measure the Site’s performance and improve the Site’s design and functionality.

## Cookies

At this time, SYNDAVER does not permanently store “cookies” on your PC and does not employ “cookies” to transmit personal information. SYNDAVER may use “session cookies,” which consist of information stored in the browser cache and passed back to the server whenever a request for a new page on the Site is made. This session cookie is not typically saved or written to disk, and the information contained in the session cookie will only be valid for that particular session. The session cookie is discarded when the browser is closed. Most web browsers automatically accept session cookies, and most may also be configured to provide notice of when a session cookie is about to be placed on the browser. No information is saved in these session cookies other than an identification number associated with the particular session.

## Use and Disclosure

Subject to applicable law, we and our Service Providers (as described below) may disclose your Personal Information:

To unaffiliated third parties that are under contract to perform services for or on behalf of SYNDAVER (Service Providers), and are required to uphold and maintain SYNDAVER’s policies with respect to privacy and the treatment of your Personal Information (e.g., vendors maintaining our computer databases or performing marketing activities for SYNDAVER relating solely to services provided by SYNDAVER and its affiliates); to other persons as permitted by applicable law or regulation; and to law enforcement personnel and agencies, or as part of a legal process, in order to protect our property or in furtherance of an investigation regarding a breach of the Site rules and policies, unauthorized access to or use of the Site or any other illegal activities.

Any access to such information will be limited to the purpose for which such information was provided to our affiliate, subsidiary or Service Provider. Our affiliates, subsidiaries and Service Providers may be located throughout the world. Accordingly, information may be sent worldwide to countries which have a different level of privacy protection than the United States.

## Consent to Processing

By using our Site, or providing information to SYNDAVER, you understand and unambiguously consent to the collection, processing, transfer and use of information in the United States and other countries and territories, for the purposes set forth in this Policy. You hereby consent to the collection and disclosure by SYNDAVER of your Personal Information as described under this Policy, including but not limited to the transfer of your Personal Information between SYNDAVER’s Service Providers and affiliates in accordance with this Policy. For further certainty, consent relating to a right to transfer information referred to in this paragraph shall be deemed to include your consent to the transfer of the applicable Personal Information to a jurisdiction which may have a different level of privacy protection than that available in your own country.

## Opt-Out Choices

To “opt-out” of (1) receiving communications from SYNDAVER (except for communications necessary for your use of the Site), (2) having your personally identifiable information used internall for marketing purposes, or (3) any other consent previously granted for a specific purpose concerning your personally identifiable information, send an e-mail to SYNDAVER using the “Contact Us” link at the top of each page.

## Reviewing Information

If you are a registered user, you may request to review, change or delete information previously provided to us by modifying your profile after “logging in” or by sending an e-mail request using the “Contact Us” link at the top of each page. Requests for changes to or deletions of your Personal Information must be made by you directly.

## Other Web Sites

This Policy applies only to www.syndaver.com. SYNDAVER, its affiliates and subsidiaries operate many web sites for different purposes and in multiple jurisdictions where local laws may apply. This Site may include links to both our affiliated sites and to non-SYNDAVER web sites, including access to content, products and services of such affiliated and non-affiliated sites (Other Sites). In some cases, these Other Sites are made available via “framing technology”, and may appear to be part of this Site. Although some of the entities controlling these framed sites may be affilliated with SYNDAVER, we urge you to familiarize yourself with the individual privacy policies and other terms for each linked or framed site prior to submitting your Personal Information.

## Transfer of Information

In the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, dissolution, or sale or transfer of substantially all of the assets of SYNDAVER, registration data and Usage Data collected from the Site may be sold or transferred to the party acquiring all or substantially all of the assets of SYNDAVER in order to permit the party to continue the operation of the Site, including the restricted areas. Subject to your ability to opt-out as described above, by using this Site and submitting your information to us, you consent to the sale and transfer of your information as described in this paragraph.

## Security

SYNDAVER takes seriously the security of the information it collects. SYNDAVER has therefore implemented technology and security policies and procedures intended to reduce the risk of accidental destruction or loss, or the unauthorized disclosure or access to, such information, reasonably appropriate to the nature of the data concerned.

## Children

Our Site is not generally intended for use by children under the age of 18, and SYNDAVER does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children in this age group. If we become aware that a user under the age of 18 has registered or is attempting to register, we will notify the user that he or she is not eligible for registration. We will then expunge any related Personal Information from our records.

## Privacy Policy Updates

SYNDAVER may, in its sole discretion, update this Policy at any time and from time to time, by posting the amended Policy on this Site. The amended Policy shall be considered to be effective upon posting, and your access to or use of the Site following an update shall be deemed consent to the revised Policy. If you are a registered user, amendments to this Policy may be sent to you via email or such other form of communication as you have requested. We urge each visitor to refer back to this page regularly and especially prior to providing or updating any Personal Information. This Policy may not be otherwise amended without the written consent of SYNDAVER. This Policy was last updated on April 14, 2011.

## Questions and Comments

If you would like to communicate with SYNDAVER regarding privacy issues or have questions, comments, or complaints about this Policy or the Site, please feel free to get in touch with us through the “Contact Us” link that resides at the top of each page.
